<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dylan Bayles&#39; Github Site</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dylan Bayles&#39; Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Is Nebraska Softball The Best Team In The Big Ten?</title>
      <link>/2022/05/01/is-nebraska-softball-the-best-team-in-the-big-ten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/05/01/is-nebraska-softball-the-best-team-in-the-big-ten/</guid>
      <description>The Nebraska Softball team has had a long history of success, with six first-place finishes in 7 years in the Big Eight during the 1980s and 15 Regional appearances at minimum in the 16 years they spent in the Big 12.
However, since moving to the Big Ten in 2012, they’ve only made two Regionals, one Super Regional, and one College World Series.
The last three years have been less than ideal with two losing seasons (one cancelled halfway due to Covid-19) followed by a 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did the Best Denver Broncos Team Actually Win a Super Bowl?</title>
      <link>/2022/04/01/did-the-best-broncos-team-actually-win-a-super-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/01/did-the-best-broncos-team-actually-win-a-super-bowl/</guid>
      <description>The Denver Broncos have been consistently bad over the last six seasons, in part due to hall of fame quarterback Peyton Manning retiring. However, they are still a highly decorated team, having won three Super Bowls (tied for 7th most) and having appeared in eight of them (tied for 3rd most). Many argue as to whether Manning or John Elway was the best Broncos quarterback of all time, but which team was the best?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the best Denver Broncos team since 1990?</title>
      <link>/2022/03/30/what-is-the-best-denver-broncos-team-since-1990/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/03/30/what-is-the-best-denver-broncos-team-since-1990/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
